debt.org 2019-03-26

# Privacy Policy - We Will Not Share Your Information

Effective Date: March 19, 2019

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes the information ClayRun LLC (“ClayRun,” “we,” or “us”) collects from or about you.  It also describes how we may use, share, and handle the information we collect.

Before using this website (the “Site”), you should review this Policy and the Terms and Conditions on this Site.  By using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, processing, use, and disclosure of your information as set forth in this Policy.  If you do not agree to be bound by this Policy, you are not authorized to, and you may not, access or use this Site.  This Policy is incorporated into our Terms and Conditions that govern your use of this Site.  You may access these Terms and Conditions by using the link provided at the bottom of each page of this Site.

ClayRun LLC reserves the right to revise this Policy at any time, in our discretion, and for any or no reason.  Such revisions shall be effective immediately upon posting such changes to this Site.  By continuing to access and use this Site, you acknowledge and agree that you shall be bound by any such revisions.  Accordingly, you should periodically review this Policy.  For your convenience, whenever this Policy is changed, we will update the “Effective Date” at the top of this page.  We encourage you to check the Effective Date to see if this Policy has been revised since your last visit.

## What Information We Collect

When you interact with us through the Site, or otherwise use or visit the Site, we may collect personal information, that is, information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us.  For example, we may collect your name, contact information, date of birth, and debt information.  In certain instances, you may have the choice to provide such information.  However, if you choose not to do so, it may impact our ability to provide you with certain services or assistance.  You may also have the opportunity to opt into receiving communications from us.  Where indicated just select the appropriate option.  We may also collect non-personally identifiable information, including through the use of cookies.

_Information from your web browser or mobile device._  You may generally visit most of our Site without telling us who you are or providing personal information.  We may collect information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser or mobile device when you visit our Site.  For example, we may collect your IP address, the name and type of your browser, and the date and time you visit our Site, depending on your browser or device settings which you may be able to change.  While this information is not, on its own, personally identifiable, we may combine it with other information that does identify you.

_Cookies and Other Technologies:_  A “cookie” is a small file placed on your device when you visit a site, such as ours.  A “session cookie” expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser).  A “persistent cookie” stores information on the hard drive so that when you end your session and return to the same web site at a later date, the cookie information is still available.  We use cookies and other technologies to collect information to improve and support functions on this Site so we can serve you better.  For example, we may use these technologies to:

  * collect information about how visitors access and use this Site, such as which pages they visit and for how long, and what functions or links they use most often; and
  * support the features and functionality of this Site and make it more personal, for example, by repopulating information you have already provided so you do not need to enter that information again.

As with your browser, we do not collect personally identifiable information using cookies and other technologies, but we may link it to personal information that you provide or that we have.  Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies.   However, you may, at any time, control the use of cookies by selecting your browser settings on your device.  You may also be able to receive an alert when a cookie is placed on your device.  If you choose to reject cookies when you access or use this Site, it may impact your ability to use all of the features and functions on this Site.

In addition to the cookies we may deliver to your computer or device through this Site, some of our third party partners may deliver cookies to you.  For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with our Sites.  To learn more about Google Analytics, [**click here**](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html).  Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer or mobile device in order to track your online behaviors over time and across nonaffiliated websites or to deliver targeted advertisements either on this Site or on other websites.  You have choices about the information third parties may collect about you through this Site.  For example, if you do not want your information sent to a third party, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by [**clicking here**](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

Please be aware that if you do not configure your browser or actively opt out, you will accept cookies provided by this Site.

## How We Use Your Information

We use the information we collect from or about you for various purposes, including: to provide you with requested information and services; to contact you as needed for your use of the Site; and to enhance our security and prevent fraud.  We understand that you may wish to make choices about how we collect, use, and share your information.  In certain instances, you may opt-out of how we or third parties collect or handle your personal information.  If you have a question about your ability to opt-out or would like to exercise this right, please contact us as provided below.

_Do Not Track Mechanisms._ Your browser may deliver a “Do-Not-Track (‘DNT’) signal,” or similar mechanism for exercising choices about the collection of information about your online activities.  Because technology continues to change, we do not guarantee that we will honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms at this time.

You may change previously-expressed preferences for how we use information you provide on or through this Site.  For example, if you have provided your contact information and receive periodic emails from us, you may choose to stop receiving those emails by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in an email’s footer.  You may be able to change other preferences through an account you create on this Site.  Otherwise, please contact us using the information provided below.

_Click-Through Agreements._ When you sign up to use special features of this Site, you may be asked to agree to special terms governing your use of the special feature.  In some cases, you may be asked to expressly consent to special terms, for example, by checking a box or clicking on a button marked “I agree.”  This type of agreement is known as a “click-through” agreement. If any terms of the click-through agreement differ from the terms of this Policy, the terms of the click-through agreement will supplement or amend this Policy and be binding upon you, but only with respect to the matters specified in the “click-through” agreement.

## Reviewing Your Information

You may contact us for assistance in order to review, update, or correct any personal information provided.  We will respond to you within a reasonable time and provide assistance to the extent possible or as required by law.

## Safeguarding Your Information

We maintain reasonable administrative, physical and technical measures to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information. Unfortunately, no website is completely secure.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed, misused or lost by accident or by the unauthorized acts of others and we expressly disclaim all liability arising therefrom.

## How We Share Your Information

All financial organizations need to share client personal information to provide the programs and services requested by the client.   In the section below, we list the primary reasons financial organizations can share their clients’ personal information; the reasons ClayRun LLC chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does ClayRun LLC Share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes**  – such as to respond to court orders and legal investigations. | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes**  – to offer programs and services to you | Yes | Yes  
**For joint marketing with other financial organizations** | Yes | Yes  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes**  – information about your creditworthiness | Yes | Yes  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
**For non-affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
**For our research and statistical analysis purposes  **– to improve our services to you and to other consumers | Yes | Yes  
  
We may offer you the opportunity to opt-out of some of our sharing, as required by applicable law, by contacting us as provided in this Policy.  You may also be able to exercise “opt out” choices by contacting the third party directly.

In relation to an ongoing or proposed business transaction (such as transferring the ownership and operation of ClayRun LLC), we may sell or transfer your information to a successor or potential successor organization, including through bankruptcy.  Any third party to whom we sell or transfer assets will have the right to continue to use your personal information in the manner described in this Policy and subject to any preferences you have expressed to us.

We may also share your information if we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate or required to comply with existing law, a court order, or a subpoena.  We may also share your personal information with law enforcement or another third party to prevent or investigate a possible crime; to protect the security of this Site; to enforce our policies and agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of others. We may also share your information with Creditors to assist in creating additional debt reduction programs.  Creditor agrees to take no additional actions other than the actions outlined in the card member agreement.  The information being provided will be used for analytical purposes only.

We may retain your personal information as needed to maintain this Site and provide you with any services; to comply with any legal obligations, meet any regulatory requirements, resolve any disputes or litigation, or as otherwise needed to enforce this Policy; and to prevent fraud and abuse.  If requested by law enforcement, we may also retain your personal information for a period of time.

## Children’s Online Privacy

This Site is not intended for children or minors under the age of eighteen years without the permission of a parent or guardian.  If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child has submitted personal information through this Site without your consent, please contact us as provided below.

## Links to Other Sites

This Site may contain links to other web sites controlled or offered by third parties.  ClayRun LLC does not control, operate, and is not responsible for the content, accuracy or opinions expressed on such third-party sites, and we do not investigate, monitor or check such sites for accuracy or completeness.  ClayRun LLC hereby disclaims any and all liability for, the privacy practices and any information, materials, products, or services posted or offered at any of the third-party sites.  ClayRun LLC does not endorse or recommend any products or services offered or information contained at such sites, nor are we liable for any failure of products and services offered or advertised at those sites.  Any information you provide to third parties on or through their websites is covered under their privacy and data collection policies and is not covered by this Policy. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information.  This Privacy Policy does not govern your use of those sites and we encourage you to review the privacy policies specifically belonging to such sites.

## Your California Privacy Rights  ** **

California residents who have an established business relationship with us may request and obtain information, free of charge and on an annual basis, about personal information that we shared with other businesses for their own direct marketing use within the prior calendar year.  If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information shared with third parties and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared this information in the immediately preceding calendar year. To obtain this information, please contact us at the number or address below and let us know you have a “California Shine the Light Privacy Request.” We will then respond to you with the requested information.

If you are a California resident and under the age of 18, you may request that we remove content or information that you have posted to our website by contacting us using the contact information below.

## Jurisdiction

This Site is operated in the State of Florida, United States of America.  If you access this Site from outside of the United States, you are responsible for compliance with any applicable laws.  The data protection laws of the country in which you reside may be more restrictive than the data protection laws of the United States.  Your personal information may be subject to disclosure under the laws of the United States or other countries to which it is transferred, and it may be accessible to law enforcement and national security authorities of those jurisdictions. By using this Site, you consent to our collection, processing, use and transfer of your personal information in or to the United States or any other country, subject to this Policy.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or would like to exercise your choices as described herein, please send us a written statement at 5750 Major Blvd, Suite 310, Orlando, Florida 32819.
